Don't run. Don't scream. Don't break the rules
Please Don't Feed the Children is a horror, thriller
film directed by Destry Allyn Spielberg.
After a viral outbreak ravaged the country’s adult population, a group of orphans heads south in search of a
new life, only to find themselves at the mercy of a deranged woman harboring a dangerous secret.
Clara, played by Michelle Dockery.
Mary, played by Zoe Colletti.
Ben, played by Andrew Liner.
Jeffy, played by Dean Scott Vazquez.
Vicky, played by Regan Aliyah.
Seth, played by Joshuah Melnick.
Please Don't Feed the Children is a 2024 American psychological thriller film
directed by Destry Allyn Spielberg and written by Paul Bertino.
It stars Michelle Dockery, Zoe Colletti, Andrew Liner, Dean Scott Vazquez, Regan
Aliyah, Emma Meisel, Joshuah Melnick, Vernon Davis, and Giancarlo Esposito.
The film had its world premiere at the 57th Sitges
Film Festival on October 11, 2024.
It was released on Tubi in the United States on June 27, 2025.
The film explores themes of child abuse, psychopath,
apocalypse, cat and mouse, children on the run.
The tone is dark and intense.